
<rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Latest Golf News, Golf Info, Sports News Updates - NDTVSports.com</title>
<link>http://sports.ndtv.com/</link>
<description>Latest Golf news, info, breaking news updates from around the cricketing world. From long on to long off, drives, hooks, pulls, cuts, yorkers and doosra, Sports.NDTV.com is an all-rounder in World Golf coverage. View best photos and videos.</description>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4992456</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/avani-prashanth-finishes-10th-as-chinese-taipei-golfer-is-crowned-champion-4992456#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Avani Prashanth Finishes 10th As Chinese Taipei Golfer Is Crowned Champion</title>
<description>India's Avani Prashanth registered her fourth straight under par round with a one-under 71 to sign off tied 10th, her best finish in the Women's Amateur Asia-Pacific Championships</description>
<a10:updated>2024-02-04T18:54:28+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4606451</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/aditi-ashok-lies-tied-second-at-andalucia-open-on-let-4606451#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Aditi Ashok Lies Tied Second At Andalucia Open On LET</title>
<description>Aditi Ashok fired a bogey-free four-under 68 that catapulted her into the tied second spot after the second round of the Andalucia Costa del Sol Open de Espana</description>
<a10:updated>2023-11-25T23:23:25+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4606443</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/joburg-open-golfer-shubhankar-sharma-makes-the-cut-4606443#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Joburg Open: Golfer Shubhankar Sharma Makes The Cut</title>
<description>Shubhankar Sharma added 1-under 69 to his first round even-par 70 to make the cut in the Joburg Open placed tied-43rd</description>
<a10:updated>2023-11-25T23:16:00+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4561350</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/dlf-golf-and-country-club-awarded-indias-best-golf-course-at-10th-annual-world-awards-4561350#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>DLF Golf And Country Club Awarded India's Best Golf Course at 10th Annual World Awards</title>
<description>DLF Golf and Country Club has been awarded the coveted title of India's Best Golf Club at the 10th Annual World Golf Awards held in Abu Dhabi recently.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-11-09T18:42:36+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4513158</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/indias-top-amateur-avani-tied-for-lead-at-world-amateur-event-team-lying-third-4513158#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Golfer Avani Prashanth Tied For Lead At World Amateur Event, Team Lying Third</title>
<description>Indian golfer Avani Prashanth continued her superb form by shooting a bogey-free 4-under 68 to take a share of the early lead in the first round of the individual section</description>
<a10:updated>2023-10-25T19:56:12+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4505189</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/diksha-dagar-finishes-sole-third-as-aline-krauter-wins-womens-indian-open-4505189#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Diksha Dagar Finishes Sole Third As Aline Krauter Wins Women's Indian Open</title>
<description>Diksha Dagar, who could have moved to the top of the Order of Merit with a win or solo second here, fumbled on the back-nine as she had just one birdie and dropped shots on the 10th and 14th.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-10-22T20:24:02+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4452441</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/golf-industry-association-announces-annual-golf-and-turf-summit-2023-4452441#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Golf Industry Association Announces Annual Golf And Turf Summit 2023</title>
<description>The Golf Industry Association (GIA) has announced the staging of its Annual GIA Golf and Turf Summit 2023</description>
<a10:updated>2023-10-05T15:33:39+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4439554</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/asian-games-2023/aditi-ashok-slips-on-final-day-signs-off-with-silver-in-womens-golf-4439554#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Asian Games: Aditi Ashok Slips On Final Day, Signs Off With Silver In Women's Golf</title>
<description>Aditi Ashok's fortunes tumbled on the final day as she carded a topsy-turvy 73 to sign off with a silver for India's first medal in women's golf</description>
<a10:updated>2023-10-01T12:33:59+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4437701</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/asian-games-2023/aditi-ashok-closes-in-on-historic-gold-indian-womens-team-marches-to-top-slot-4437701#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Asian Games, Golf: Aditi Ashok Closes In On Historic Gold; Indian Women's Team In Top Slot</title>
<description>Aditi Ashok played a sensational third round of 11-under 61 to place herself in a commanding position to win a historic individual gold medal in the golf competition</description>
<a10:updated>2023-09-30T14:18:07+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4435105</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/asian-games-2023/aditi-stays-t-2-womens-team-third-lahiri-ninth-in-men-s-section-at-asian-games-4435105#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Golf: Aditi Ashok Stays T-2, Women's Team Third; Anirban Lahiri 9th In Men's Section At Asian Games</title>
<description>Indian golfer Aditi Ashok continued to stay in medal contention in the individual event as she was just one shot behind the leader at tied second</description>
<a10:updated>2023-09-29T17:25:27+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4424553</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/asian-games-2023/strong-indian-golf-team-eyes-asian-games-medals-4424553#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Strong Indian Golf Team Eyes Asian Games 2023 Medals</title>
<description>The seven-member Indian golf team, comprising the likes of Anirban Lahiri and Aditi Ashok, will be hoping to carry forward its recent superb form when the event commences at the Asian Games on Thursday.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-09-26T16:10:24+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4348471</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/manu-gandas-shubhankar-sharma-struggle-in-first-round-at-crans-montana-4348471#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Manu Gandas, Shubhankar Sharma Struggle In First Round At Crans-Montana</title>
<description>Indian golfers Manu Gandas and Shubhankar Sharma struggled in the first round of the Omega European Masters and were placed tied 68th and tied 122nd respectively.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-09-01T17:40:49+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4328231</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/lahiri-ahlawat-among-six-leaders-after-first-round-at-st-andrews-4328231#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Anirban Lahiri, Veer Ahlawat Among Six Leaders After First Round At St Andrews</title>
<description>India's Anirban Lahiri continued his fine run as he opened the inaugural St Andrews Bay Championship with a superb 6-under 66 that gave him a share in the six-way lead</description>
<a10:updated>2023-08-25T16:02:43+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4315108</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/lahiri-finishes-third-in-newcastle-4315108#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Anirban Lahiri Finishes Third In Newcastle</title>
<description>Indian golfer Anirban Lahiri shot a fine 3-under 68 in the final round but failed to find as many birdies as he deserved to finish third at the International Series England.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-08-21T16:21:51+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4285579</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/aditi-ashok-diksha-dagar-to-play-at-womens-british-open-4285579#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Aditi Ashok, Diksha Dagar To Play At Women's British Open</title>
<description>Aditi Ashok and Diksha Dagar will feature in the Women's British Open from Thursday in what is the final major tournament of the year for women.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-08-10T17:17:38+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4234892</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/shubhankar-achieves-best-ever-result-by-an-indian-at-open-finishes-eighth-4234892#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Shubhankar Sharma Achieves Best Ever Result By An Indian At Open, Finishes Eighth</title>
<description>Shubhankar Sharma, playing his third Open, was the only player on the final day logging a bogey-free round of 1-under 70 for a total of 5-under 279.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-07-24T02:11:03+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4232144</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/playing-his-best-links-golf-shubhankar-sharma-lies-fourth-at-halfway-mark-at-the-open-4232144#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Playing His Best Links Golf, Shubhankar Sharma Lies Fourth At Halfway Mark At The Open</title>
<description>India's Shubhankar Shama held his own in the company of the best golfers in the world, carding an even par 71 to share the fourth place at the Open</description>
<a10:updated>2023-07-22T17:47:41+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4151682</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/diksha-dagar-wins-record-second-ladies-european-tour-event-title-4151682#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Diksha Dagar Wins Record Second Ladies European Tour Event Title</title>
<description>Diksha Dagar finally cruised to her second Ladies European Tour as she grabbed a commanding four-shot win at the Czech Ladies Open on Sunday.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-06-25T19:36:28+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4117027</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/mistaken-for-a-fan-pro-golfer-tackled-by-security-guard-during-canadian-open-match-watch-4117027#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Watch: Mistaken For A Fan, Pro Golfer Tackled By Security Guard In Canadian Open</title>
<description>In a video doing rounds on the social media, Hadwin was seen popping a champagne to celebrate Taylor's victory when a security in-charge came and pinned him to the ground</description>
<a10:updated>2023-06-14T09:26:01+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4088182</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/harjai-milkha-wins-title-cheema-and-mahreen-finish-second-in-us-kids-europeans-4088182#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Harjai Milkha Wins Title, Cheema And Mahreen Finish 2nd In US Kids Europeans</title>
<description>With seven birdies against four bogeys, Harjai Milkha Singh beat his closest opponent by two shots.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-06-02T15:36:05+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3845444</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/tiger-woods-ex-girlfriend-suing-over-acrimonious-split-court-filing-3845444#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Tiger Woods' Ex-Girlfriend Suing Over Acrimonious Split: Court Filing</title>
<description>Erica Herman, who lived with the 15-time major winner at his Florida mansion until late 2022, filed the request in the Circuit Court of the 19th Judicial Circuit in Martin County, Florida.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-03-09T10:24:03+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3755630</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/aditi-ashok-wins-by-9-shots-in-dominating-show-in-kenya-takes-fourth-let-title-3755630#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Aditi Ashok Wins By 9 Shots In Dominating Show In Kenya, Takes Fourth LET Title</title>
<description>Aditi Ashok turned in one of the most dominating performances on the Ladies European Tour with a nine-shot win at the Magical Kenya Ladies Open on Sunday.</description>
<a10:updated>2023-02-05T21:04:22+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3568721</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/its-a-flawed-system-tiger-woods-wants-world-golf-ranking-system-to-be-changed-3568721#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>"It's A Flawed System": Tiger Woods Wants World Golf Ranking System To be Changed</title>
<description>The Official World Golf Ranking (OWGR), which was revamped in August to make it more equitable, has been criticised by top golfers such as Jon Rahm, who termed it "laughable".</description>
<a10:updated>2022-12-01T14:00:35+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3561713</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/difficult-to-walk-woods-withdraws-from-hero-world-challenge-due-to-foot-injury-3561713#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>"Difficult To Walk": Tiger Woods Withdraws From Hero World Challenge Due To Foot Injury</title>
<description>Tournament host Tiger Woods was forced to pull out of this week's Hero World Challenge due to a foot injury that is "making it difficult to walk."</description>
<a10:updated>2022-11-29T09:46:32+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3500698</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/argentine-golf-champion-angel-cabrera-sentenced-again-for-assault-3500698#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Argentine Golf Champion Angel Cabrera Sentenced Again For Assault</title>
<description>Argentine golf champion Angel Cabrera was on Monday convicted for the second time of assaulting an ex-partner.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-11-08T15:06:22+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3485920</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/from-sickly-child-to-world-number-one-thai-golfer-atthaya-thitikul-chases-tiger-woods-tail-3485920#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>From Sickly Child To World Number One, Thai Golfer Atthaya Thitikul Chases Tiger Wood's Tail</title>
<description>Thai teenager Atthaya Thitikul reached the top of the world women's golf rankings this week after a stunning debut year on the LPGA Tour</description>
<a10:updated>2022-11-03T12:20:46+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3478966</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/thailands-atthaya-thitikul-19-becomes-womens-golf-number-one-3478966#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Thailand's Atthaya Thitikul, 19, Becomes Women's Golf Number One</title>
<description>Atthaya Thitikul is only the second player under 20 to reach number one</description>
<a10:updated>2022-11-01T10:59:07+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3466610</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/with-cricketer-dad-nikhil-chopraa-as-caddie-krishnav-off-to-solid-start-in-asia-pacific-amateur-golf-3466610#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>With Cricketer Dad Nikhil Chopraa As Caddie, Krishnav Off To Solid Start In Asia-Pacific Amateur Golf</title>
<description>Debutant Krishnav Nikhil Chopraa shot five birdies against one bogey and a double to be placed Tied-20th, the best among seven Indians, on the opening day of the 13th Asia Pacific Amateur Championships, on Thursday</description>
<a10:updated>2022-10-27T17:20:49+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3302848</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/liv-can-be-the-ipl-of-golf-anirban-lahiri-on-breakaway-series-3302848#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>"LIV Can Be The IPL Of Golf": Anirban Lahiri On Breakaway Series</title>
<description>The breakaway LIV series can do for golf what the IPL did for cricket, India's top player Anirban Lahiri has said after joining the lucrative Saudi-backed tour.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-08-31T14:44:41+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3300972</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/anirban-lahiri-becomes-first-indian-to-sign-up-with-rebel-liv-golf-tour-3300972#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Anirban Lahiri Becomes First Indian To Sign Up With Rebel Liv Golf Tour</title>
<description>Anirban Lahiri becomes the first Indian and the first Asian to sign up with Liv Golf.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-08-30T20:31:44+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3177985</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/henrik-stenson-stripped-of-ryder-cup-captaincy-as-liv-rumours-swirl-3177985#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Henrik Stenson Stripped Of Ryder Cup Captaincy As LIV Rumours Swirl</title>
<description>The move will deepen the rifts in the sport, with a growing number of big stars defecting to the cash-rich new circuit in defiance of the established tours.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-07-20T22:02:17+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3162597</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/british-open-tearful-tiger-woods-misses-cut-in-likely-st-andrews-farewell-3162597#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>British Open: Tearful Tiger Woods Misses Cut In Likely St Andrews Farewell</title>
<description>A tearful Tiger Woods said he may never get the chance to grace a British Open at St Andrews again after missing the cut on Friday with a score of nine-over-par for his two rounds.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-07-15T23:27:19+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3091363</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/liv-golf-rebels-allowed-to-play-in-british-open-3091363#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>LIV Golf Rebels Allowed To Play In British Open</title>
<description>The US PGA Tour has banned those involved in the rebel venture after the inaugural event in Britain earlier this month but organisers of last week's US Open did not follow suit</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-22T20:21:43+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3082422</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/matt-fitzpatrick-wins-us-open-golf-tournament-with-sensational-finish-3082422#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>England's Matt Fitzpatrick Wins US Open Golf Tournament With Sensational Finish</title>
<description>Matt Fitzpatrick captured his first major title on Sunday by winning the US Open in dramatic fashion, making spectacular shots as rivals crumbled under final-round pressure.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-20T08:42:55+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3077909</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/collin-morikawa-shares-us-open-lead-jon-rahm-and-rory-mcilroy-one-adrift-3077909#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Collin Morikawa Shares US Open Lead, Jon Rahm And Rory McIlroy One Adrift</title>
<description>A weekend showdown of golf's top stars was set Friday at the US Open as two-time major winner Collin Morikawa seized a share of the lead while Jon Rahm and Rory McIlroy were one stroke adrift.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-18T08:25:51+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3076023</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/us-open-resumes-with-adam-hadwin-ahead-stormy-scene-for-rory-mcilroy-3076023#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>US Open Resumes With Adam Hadwin Ahead, Stormy Scene For Rory McIlroy</title>
<description>Leader Adam Hadwin was set for a morning start as Friday's second round of the US Open began while Rory McIlroy and defending champion Jon Rahm could have to face afternoon thunderstorms</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-17T16:57:53+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3057510</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/former-us-open-champion-bryson-dechambeau-joins-saudi-backed-rebel-golf-series-3057510#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Former US Open Champion Bryson DeChambeau Joins Saudi-Backed Rebel Golf Series</title>
<description>Former US Open champion Bryson DeChambeau has become the latest star to sign up to the rebel LIV Golf series, the organisers announced.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-11T08:32:10+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3049276</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/phil-mickelson-says-he-does-not-condone-human-rights-violations-on-eve-of-new-series-3049276#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Phil Mickelson Says He Does Not "Condone Human Rights Violations" On Eve Of New Series</title>
<description>Phil Mickelson said Wednesday he does not condone human rights violations in Saudi Arabia, on the eve of the first tournament of the divisive LIV Golf Invitational Series near London funded by the Gulf kingdom</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-08T17:01:02+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3047414</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/tiger-woods-says-he-will-miss-us-open-next-week-3047414#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Tiger Woods Says He Will Miss US Open Next Week</title>
<description>The 46-year-old made a surprise return at the Masters in April, after needing surgery to repair his right leg following the car crash in February 2021.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-08T00:09:51+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3045757</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/dustin-johnson-former-world-no-1-golfer-quits-pga-tour-3045757#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Former World No.1 Golfer Dustin Johnson Quits PGA Tour</title>
<description>Former world number one golfer Dustin Johnson confirmed on Tuesday he has resigned his membership of the US PGA Tour as he prepares to play in the breakaway LIV Golf Invitational Series.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-07T18:23:30+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3034251</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/hideki-matsuyama-disqualified-from-pga-memorial-over-club-infraction-3034251#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Hideki Matsuyama Disqualified From PGA Memorial Over Club Infraction</title>
<description>Japanese star Hideki Matsuyama was disqualified from the PGA Tour's Memorial tournament in bizarre circumstances on Thursday after officials found an illegal substance on his 3-wood.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-06-03T09:00:58+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3000696</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/golfer-aditi-ashok-tweets-french-airlines-over-missing-kit-bag-3000696#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Golfer Aditi Ashok Tweets French Airlines Over Missing Kit Bag</title>
<description>Golfer Aditi Ashok on Monday took to Twitter to request French airlines to help find her missing kit bag</description>
<a10:updated>2022-05-23T13:47:17+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3000021</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/justin-thomas-sensational-comeback-seals-pga-victory-after-mito-pereira-collapse-3000021#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Justin Thomas' Sensational Comeback Seals PGA Victory After Mito Pereira Collapse</title>
<description>Justin Thomas matched the greatest last-day comeback in PGA Championship history on Sunday, roaring back from seven strokes down at Southern Hills to capture his second major title.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-05-23T08:55:57+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2989637</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/indian-golf-star-plays-practice-round-with-tiger-woods-ahead-of-pga-championship-2989637#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Indian Golf Star Plays Practice Round With Tiger Woods Ahead of PGA Championship</title>
<description>Anirban Lahiri has played once previously with Tiger Woods over three holes when the American superstar jetted into New Delhi in 2014 for a flying visit. But since competing on the PGA TOUR in 2016, the Indian has had the chance to know the 82-time PGA TOUR winner over time.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-05-19T13:01:46+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2968532</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/diksha-dagar-claims-gold-medal-at-deaflympics-2968532#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Diksha Dagar Claims Gold Medal At Deaflympics</title>
<description>Indian golfer Diksha Dagar outplayed American Ashlyn Grace in the final to bag gold medal at the Deaflympics, fulfilling her promise of improving upon the silver-winning performance at the 2017 edition.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-05-12T13:15:54+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2942309</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/ab-de-villiers-hopes-grass-is-greener-for-golf-teammate-ashleigh-barty-2942309#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>AB De Villiers Hopes Grass Is Greener For Golf Teammate Ashleigh Barty</title>
<description>AB de Villiers first met avid cricket fan Ashleigh Barty when he was playing in Australia's Big Bash League in 2019 and they will meet again when they team up in the inaugural Icons Series golf event in Jersey City from June 30 to July 1.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-05-03T16:47:06+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2934335</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/viraj-madappa-rashid-khan-among-men-avani-prashanth-in-women-book-asian-games-golf-berths-2934335#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Viraj Madappa, Rashid Khan Among Men, Avani Prashanth In Women Book Asian Games Golf Berths</title>
<description>Viraj Madappa and Rashid Khan kept their nerves and held their rivals at bay to earn the coveted Asian Games berths in golf after a gruelling five-round affair, on Saturday.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-04-30T16:16:24+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2893722</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/thought-i-would-never-play-golf-again-jeev-milkha-singh-2893722#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Thought I Would Never Play Golf Again: Jeev Milkha Singh</title>
<description>Jeev Milkha Singh said that he didn't think he would play golf again after the death of his parents due to COVID-19 last year.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-04-16T19:54:31+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2876873</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/world-no-1-scottie-scheffler-wins-first-major-at-masters-tiger-woods-finishes-47th-2876873#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>World No.1 Scottie Scheffler Wins First Major At Masters, Tiger Woods Finishes 47th</title>
<description>Top-ranked Scottie Scheffler captured his first major title on Sunday by winning the Masters in dominating fashion, holding firm down the stretch to seize the green jacket after Tiger Woods completed his comeback from severe leg injuries.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-04-11T07:57:23+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2874839</guid>
<link>https://sports.ndtv.com/golf/masters-2022-tiger-woods-challenge-fades-scottie-scheffler-in-command-2874839#rss-sports-golf</link>
<title>Masters 2022: Tiger Woods' Challenge Fades, Scottie Scheffler In Command</title>
<description>Tiger Woods' hopes of a victorious return from career-threatening injuries evaporated on Augusta National's greens on Saturday while Scottie Scheffler seized a three-stroke Masters lead.</description>
<a10:updated>2022-04-10T08:44:13+05:30</a10:updated>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>